babylon-booking.com 2017-11-14

# Privacy Policy | Babylon Booking

## Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy Overview

At Moonline Travel and Trade Ltd (hereinafter referred to as Moonline) we understand that data privacy is a very important issue. We are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal details every time you make purchases online and considers customer information safety a matter of great importance. 

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on Babylon-Booking.com (hereinafter referred to as Babylon Booking). By using our portal, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. 

Please note that this Policy applies only to information collected by our portal and not to information collected or obtained by other means or media. Our policy ensures that any information you provide us remains private and secure. 

This privacy policy is applicable to Babylon-Booking.com only and does not apply to any affiliated websites/portals or any other third party websites, even if they are linked with the Babylon-booking.com website. It is recommended that you read the private policy of the other parties you interact with. 

We use Personal Information in order to provide you with information on Babylon Booking, in order to properly provide you with our services. 

Personal information provided by you at the time of registration or making online payment are the only mandatory submission you are required to make as a user. 

### Information Collection and Use

Your use of Babylon Booking portal constitutes a business relationship and agreement wherein we provide travel and tourism related services for your use. In exchange, Moonline reserves the right to use the contact information collected during site submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our services, to provide free newsletters, to inform you of additions to Babylon Booking portal or to send important announcements. 

When you make reservations/bookings we might be obligated to provide appropriate personal information to third parties agencies/suppliers to facilitate your travel arrangements. 

Personal information, which includes name, IP address, email address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card information, and travel information, etc. that the client provides voluntarily will be transmitted using secure SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption, which enables your browser to scramble and encode your information before it is transmitted to our servers. 

You may remove yourself from any or all of our notice and announcement mailings at anytime if you wish so. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid company email address. 

### Registration

Users are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, email etc. The personal information collected from Users during the registration process is used to manage each User’s account (such as for billing purposes, etc). Moonline does not rent or sell email addresses nor any other personal data. 

In instances where Moonline and an affiliated company or a partner jointly promote the Services, Moonline may provide the partner certain personal information who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the outcome of the promotion. In this case, the partner may not use personal information for any other purpose. 

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Moonline may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control the use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

### Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected server. Access is restricted to Moonline staff only. 

Moonline does not store any credit card information, as all transactions are processed by PayPal or other third party approved Credit Card processor. 

### Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition of Moonline with another entity or multiple entities, all (or selected proportion) of Babylon Booking customer information (including email addresses) may be transferred to a separate entity or entities. All Babylon Booking subscribers and registered users have to check and review the Privacy Policy to become aware of any changes in the policies. Subscribers and users may choose to access and modify any of their registration and subscription information at that time. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is reviewed from time to time and periodic changes may be made to our policies in regards to those reviews. It is advised to check back on this page to ensure that you have the latest version of our privacy policy.
